OUR STICKY LOVE
Chairman, sir.
Prosecutor Go isn't on the cargo ship.
Baek Sang-gil!
So we meet like this.
I used to call you Coach.
But what should I call you now?
There isn't really a way
for an abandoned disciple
to address their master.
1991 NATIONAL BOXING TEAM
FINAL SELECTION
LIGHT WELTERWEIGHT MATCHUP
BAEK SANG-GIL
VS LEE JUNG-GU
Baek Sang-gil is in great form today.
At this rate, Baek Sang-gil's gold medal
is almost guaranteed.
No holding.
Baek Sang-gil is really going for it.
No holding. Break!
Stop!
What's going on here?
Blue corner.
You forfeit. It's over.
Baek Sang-gil's coach
just threw in the towel.
It's not uncommon for a coach
to throw in the towel
to protect their fighter at risk.
But, in this case,
Baek Sang-gil had the upper hand.
-Exactly.
-It's a little baffling.
Baek Sang-gil also looks
very confused right now.
Coach!
What the heck did you…
Take them off.
Thought I wouldn't hear
the difference in your gloves?
I had it in the bag. I was so close
to becoming a national athlete.
You think you can become
a national athlete with such dirty fists?
Wouldn't it be good for you
if I make the national team?
Taking you in as my disciple,
even for a short time,
will have been
the most shameful thing in my life.
-Coach!
-From this moment on, I'm not your coach.
I never taught you
to use your fists to harm others.
Fuck this!
I cherish Jang Tae-ha as if he were made
from my own rib.
And soon, not only me
but all of Korea will come to cherish him
as a great athlete.
Your disciple who wound up on
the same path as me, whom you despised.
I'm sure it wasn't easy to take him back.
I'm truly sorry
things turned out this way.
You know what?
The thrill of throwing punches
with your life on the line
makes those pretty little jabs in the ring
pale in comparison.
Even after 30 years,
you haven't changed one bit,
Baek Sang-gil.
Do you think you corrupted
someone I care about?
You didn't.
Tae-ha
has never been corrupted.
Even now, you're trying
to kill innocent folks for your own greed.
But Tae-ha did all this
to save someone's life.
So
you've got nothing to be proud of.
I reported a car explosion,
so the police will be here soon.
If you have the guts,
stay and see what happens.
Tae-ha.
Are you okay?
Can you get up?
Try to get up.
I told you not to get involved.
Why did you come?
Even if you had Gang-rok, the gas cans,
and were ready to call the police,
what if something went wrong?
How could you go at him like that?
Still… Go Eun-sae got away.
Safely.
She got away safely.
No, Jang Tae-ha!
Tae-ha.
Tae-ha!
Stay with me. Tae-ha!
Hey, stay with me! Tae-ha!
-Let go.
-I won't. We have to go.
I have to go now!
If you do, you'll die.
I said let go of me!
Step on their foot,
trip them up,
and run away.
Ms. Go Eun-sae!
Damn it.
I'M DONE
LEAVE AT THE COAST GUARD SIREN
What the… Eun-sae?
Kaito?
Just don't disappear without a word.
Just stay out of danger.
Just…
Just stay safe.
Park Hyo-jin.
You bitch.
Is it back?
Your memory?
Yeah,
you bitch.
What's with the bag of taffy?
All I knew was
that you were in some taffy village,
so what else could I do?
You deleted your Instagram account,
and I lost your new phone number.
Why bother searching for a bitch
you hate so much?
If you got your revenge,
you should've moved on for good.
You don't even have the guts to do that.
It all came back to me.
Hey, switch shoes with me.
Hey.
The hurt kept piling up,
and I'd forgotten about
all the good times we'd shared.
But after I got my revenge on you,
all the hurt disappeared,
and I could see it again.
The good times we had.
And the sort of friend you used to be.
I'm sorry.
I lived my life wrong.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry for everything.
I'm more sorry.
No. I'm even more sorry.
Eun-sae, drink this while it's warm.
Thanks.
Where were you, really?
Gujin.
Gujin? Right, Gujin.
So there's a taffy village there too.
And who was the person who took you in?
He was… someone that I knew.
What's your name?
Jang Tae-ha.
We had met before,
and he was someone
who left me with a good memory.
But I like this one the most.
I met my first love here.
It was nice meeting you,
Mr. Future Gold Medalist.
And it turned out
that we'd first crossed paths
a very long time ago.
MIRAE EDEN COMPANY
ORGANIZATIONAL CHART
JANG TAE-HA
DIRECTOR
I'm sorry that I was
a gangster.
He was an unfortunate person
who lived a life he never wanted.
It's me.
Jang Tae-ha.
Your boyfriend.
We met in the mountains.
Our dog isn't in the yard.
I'll hurry and go find her.
He even put on a clumsy act.
Don't take it too hard.
If you keep living…
everything passes.
He's the one who saved me.
Eun-sae.
He risked his life to save me
until the very end.
What was that?
You mean Prosecutor Go
didn't get on the boat?
Then where is Eun-sae right now?
I don't know.
The last thing I saw
was her riding off on my motorcycle.
-Good heavens.
-Goodness, what do we do?
Tae-ha will freak if he finds out.
But even if he does find out,
there's no way for us to find her.
She turned her phone off,
and we can't just…
ask the police for help either.
Goodness. What are we gonna do?
Let's not tell Tae-ha for now.
If that punk finds out
she didn't get on the boat,
he'll leave this place in a flash
and scour the entire country for her.
-Yeah.
-Yes, I agree with you.
Instead, I'll look into the facilities
across the country.
Yeah, okay.
Thank goodness.
I'm so glad you had him.
There's only one thing I can do
for Jang Tae-ha.
I need to catch Baek Sang-gil.
-You're going back to work?
-No, I need to see how things go first.
If they put me on long-term leave,
Baek Sang-gil must have people
in the Prosecutor's Office.
Baek Sang-gil tortured me
to find out where my watch was.
And in the end, he found it. I saw it.
But even after finding it,
he didn't kill me.
That means
he knows about my plan B.
And the only person who knows about that
is Chi-hyeon.
Actually, when I mentioned
that I was going to report you missing…
She's not missing.
…Chi-hyeon told me not to,
saying you weren't missing.
But something felt off about it.
Does that mean he's also…
He's likely to be one of them.
How could he…
Then what was plan B?
My sneakers.
My sneakers were set to instantly upload
whatever they filmed to my cloud drive.
But when I tried to access the drive
earlier from my phone, I couldn't.
I think they hacked my account too.
Then what do we do?
There is a way.
I had the cameras in my watch and sneakers
synced to my laptop.
So the footage should be saved
on my laptop at home.
But
I'm scared to go home right now.
In case Baek Sang-gil's people
might have done something to it?
Yeah.
So, I was wondering…
-How did it go?
-There were no suspicious vehicles.
And there were no bugs or cameras
around your home either.
But there were signs that someone
had tampered with the door lock.
-Sorry?
We did a thorough check of the place.
It's safe, so you can go in.
Okay, thank you.
What? Your laptop.
Your laptop is gone.
Those bastards must have taken
your laptop too.
Of course.
Baek Sang-gil is a meticulous bastard.
So what now?
Is it saved anywhere else?
It's not. The memory chip in the sneakers
is the last place.
Where are they?
They found no viable fingerprints
on the clothes and shoes you were wearing
when you were found.
Why did I wear a suit with sneakers
instead of dress shoes that day?
So unstylish.
In Taffy Village.
That's great. Then let's ask
that Jang Tae-ha guy for help.
And tell him you got your memory back.
We can't do that. If he finds out
my memory's back, he won't just stand by.
He'll definitely try to send me somewhere
or try to protect me.
He'd disrupt the investigation.
I don't want to put him in more danger
because of me.
Then what will you do?
Chairman.
I think Prosecutor Go is in Korea.
What?
I confirmed that no ships left the port
overnight except that cargo ship.
And some of our men saw her
leaving the port on a motorcycle.
Why did you come
when Prosecutor Go isn't even here?
You had the nerve to hide Prosecutor Go
and thought I'd just sit still?
You must be upset
about your dear disciple,
but I always make sure to repay my debts,
favors, and grudges.
Even you praised my tenacity
when I was a boxer, did you not?
If you're going to play the "former coach"
and give me some half-baked advice…
Can't you just
let Tae-ha go now?
Prosecutor Go has lost her memory,
so she can't do you any harm.
If it's me you hate,
then do whatever you want
to me.
Let Tae-ha go.
Let him go.
That poor boy has never lived for himself
his entire life.
Please.
Just leave him…
alone now.
I'm…
begging you.
KAITO
I told you,
I spoke with Kaito on the phone.
He said the boat departed safely.
But… I still haven't heard from him, so…
No news is good news.
He'll call when everything's settled.
Get some rest. That's it.
You're up?
-What took you so long at the store?
-Did you stop by somewhere?
Yeah, the bathroom.
Hey, don't worry about others
going to the bathroom.
Worry about yourself.
You're a healthy young man,
not an old man.
What are you doing in a hospital bed?
That's why I'm going home now.
-Goodness.
-Already?
Hey, I didn't mean it like that.
I'm really fine.
There's nothing to do here anyway.
You should recover more…
Stay a bit longer.
-No, I…
-I'm fine.
That's not what I meant.
-Watch your step.
-Careful.
I'll go check Tae-ha's room.
I said stay a bit longer.
Why were you in such a rush to leave?
Should he lie down?
-Hold on.
-Are you okay?
-Grandma.
-Ma'am, you're here?
-Ma'am.
-Ma'am, please.
Tae-ha's condition right now is…
Ma'am, please.
How much more of an inconsiderate
grandmother do you want me to be?
I heard you didn't go because of me.
You like her so much,
but you didn't go
because of my illness again.
How do you expect me to live?
This grandmother,
who held back her grandson twice…
How can I continue to live
with this shame?
And you? How are you going to live?
You let the girl you love
more than your own life go off on her own.
How are you going to live?
Grandma.
It's okay, Grandma.
I can live just fine
even without her.
I'll live just fine.
My poor baby. My baby.
What am I going to do, my baby?
Will you really be okay alone?
Don't worry and go to work.
The security company confirmed it's safe,
and Baek Sang-gil thinks I went to Japan.
So it's actually safer here right now.
Okay. Call me right away
if anything happens.
Okay.
Thank you, Hyo-jin.
Don't be silly.
Don't come out barefoot.
It's okay.
Go inside.
-Okay.
-See you!
They say you don't know when someone
comes, but you know when they leave.
The entire village has gone so quiet
all because Eun-sae has gone.
I wonder if she has arrived safely
in Japan yet.
Stop it, you two.
Why are you thinking about someone
who's gone?
Have you already forgotten me?
Leaving only longing behind…
Light pink roses.
Have you really forgotten me?
They're so pretty.
They were her favorite.
We had so much fun at karaoke.
And she fought like a trooper.
It's no good if it won't work!
Then I guess we should call it a day.
It was such a comfort,
having that feisty hen in my corner.
Oh, what am I to do when I miss you so?
My longing for you only grows
BREAKFAST, LUNCH, DINNER
Easy. Wait, the cushions.
You can go now. I'm fine.
No, it's okay.
I should be here to help you.
You're not well, so it must be hard
for you to wash up alone too.
Even so, you shouldn't be the one
washing me.
-Go now before it gets more awkward.
-Okay.
Okay, then.
Call me if you need anything urgently.
I'll always be one step behind you.
Okay.
Okay, good.
Gang-rok.
Yes? Yes, sir.
You should be careful.
Baek Sang-gil knows that you're here
and that you helped me.
Well, why would he care about
someone like me?
Don't worry.
I might not be as good as you,
but I'm still a pretty good fight…
Who are you? Who do you work for, damn it!
Sir, I've still got it.
Don't worry.
Please rest.
Sir, if anything happens,
please contact me immediately.
Good morning.
She must have arrived safely, right?
I wonder if she'll find some comfort
in living there.
This place is so beautiful.
I bet living somewhere like this
would feel like a dream.
I hope she's not having too hard a time.
Go Eun-sae.
That's not her name.
Her name is Blessing.
I chose it as it's a blessing
for her to have settled here.
What…
What happened?
Why are you here?
"What happened?"
After doing something so huge to me,
how can you ask what happened?
I was so scared, I could've died.
Man, this is crazy.
Why didn't you go to Japan?
Why would I go to Japan?
Stowaway? Why would I have to stow away?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Because you'd be safe that way.
I can be safe without going.
I can just
break up with Jang Tae-ha.
-What?
-Why are you so surprised?
You knew I hated gangsters.
If you were going back,
you should've prepared to lose me.
The reason you sent me away was
that you went back to being a gangster.
So if I ended things with you,
wouldn't I be safe?
Even if that's true,
you have nowhere to go right now.
I'll go to a facility.
And we're strangers now,
so don't ask me any more questions.
Did…
some of your memory
come back?
No. What, I can't break up with you
if my memory hasn't returned?
I came here to say we're breaking up,
and I'll be fine.
Thanks for taking care of me until now.
I'll just take my things and leave.
What…
Wait, what…
Where are all my things?
I sent everything to Japan yesterday.
What?
I asked Mr. Hong to send your things
after we left.
But why… How could you…
Call and ask them to send it back
right away.
Something important is in there.
-Hurry.
-Okay.
Hurry.
What did they say?
If they send it back right away,
it should arrive by tomorrow afternoon.
Tomorrow afternoon?
What do I do?
I guess I have no choice but to
stay here tonight.
The package won't get here until tomorrow.
It'd be impractical to go to Seoul today
and come back tomorrow.
You must've already said you want
to break up. How tragically funny.
Yeah, I know.
Well, I guess you have no choice.
Enjoy the sleepover.
I'm with Go Eun-sae now.
Call me when you see this.
Don't you dare try to ship me off again.
I'm not someone who obediently goes
wherever you tell me to go.
You were never particularly
obedient.
It seems like you really let yourself go
while I was gone.
What?
I just left the hospital.
I can't believe you.
What are you doing? Go take a shower.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
I'm sorry.
You're more hurt than I thought.
Then
you mustn't be able to shower on your own.
Right?
There's nothing to wash.
But I have a lot of hair.
I meant that you have a small head.
I can dry it myself.
Just stay put.
I can just break up with Jang Tae-ha.
Now you look better.
Was I that hideous to look at?
Yes.
-Which facility are you going to?
-I told you not to ask.
I told you, we broke up.
We can still stay in--
You've never washed her, right?
What?
No.
I knew it.
Everyone in this house ends up so dirty
if I'm not around.
Come on, follow me.
I wonder if she'll turn into a white dog.
-My eyes.
-It's in your eyes?
-The soap…
-Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Ma'am!
We stopped by
because we heard you were here.
Yeah, so we came in a hurry.
But… should we come back later?
No…
Are you feeling okay, Eun-sae?
You all knew I was going far away,
but you kept it from me.
But what happened?
Where were you all this time?
Jang Tae-ha can fill you in.
Where are you going?
I'm going to get something for our dinner.
Don't follow me, Jang Tae-ha.
Explain to them what's going on.
And catch Blessing and bathe her.
Hey, what the heck?
Why is she suddenly so cold to you?
What happened?
You should have told me
if you knew she hadn't gone.
That was because
we knew you'd go looking for her
even though you were in no state to.
But I'm really glad
Eun-sae showed up safe and sound.
But she can't stay in Taffy Village
anymore, right?
Since Baek Sang-gil knows about it,
it's not as safe as it used to be.
I asked Kaito to find out
when the next stowaway boat will leave,
but it'll take a while.
And it won't be easy
to convince Go Eun-sae.
On that note,
did you happen to see an odd suit
and sneakers when you packed her stuff?
-Did you see them?
-No.
Did you see them?
Odd?
I think the plan B evidence
Baek Sang-gil is looking for
is in the outfit Go Eun-sae was wearing
at the time of the incident.
Somewhere like the buttons on the suit,
the belt, or the sneakers.
That makes sense.
We'll have to look for that first
when her stuff comes back.
If we find that evidence,
we may be able to keep her safe
without having to send her away.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
NAME: MIN SU-JI
Maybe hating me
will make it hurt a little less.
What are you doing?
You asked to see me,
and now you've gone quiet?
What?
Right, I…
I… realized something recently.
I'd been standing in a field of flowers.
Some people are forced to break up
even when they love someone
enough to risk their lives.
Even fighting over our pride like this
feels like a luxury.
I wanted to say…
I'm sorry for everything.
For the times I didn't mean to,
and the times I did mean to hurt you
the way I did.
I'm sorry for everything.
And…
I really liked you a lot, Min Su-ji.
I actually don't really like yulmu tea.
But when I ordered it,
I was able to see you some more,
so I ordered several cups.
Here's your yulmu tea.
Thanks.
I just love yulmu tea.
When I dated you,
someone who I liked so much,
I really felt like
I had the whole world.
But people are so fickle and petty.
I forgot all about that.
So now I'll
respect your decision.
You can stop coming to the clinic.
An Gi-jun…
And, as you wanted,
let's break up now.
I'll get going, then.
This isn't really
your type of cuisine, is it?
I guess my taste buds changed
after I almost died.
Everyone, dig in.
-Okay.
-Thank you for the food.
-I don't know what to start with.
-This looks good.
-I've never tried this.
-I can't even make this.
You're in your twenties, Gang-rok.
They say black chicken legs are good
for people in their thirties and older.
I guess that means I qualify.
Yeah, you do.
Abalone.
The abalone smells a bit fishy.
You should eat this, Jang Tae-ha.
You should eat some too.
Yeah, thanks.
I can eat the chicken neck, right?
Eat some shrimp too.
Long time no see, shrimp.
There's a lot of kimchi. Eat up.
Wow, so much kimchi.
I ate, but I'm still hungry.
Didn't it seem like the menu was
for Tae-ha's health and recovery?
Yeah.
And if they're about to break up,
isn't it weird that she said
she'd sleep over?
She has our place.
And the S.E.S ladies' places too.
She didn't have to…
That's what I'm saying.
What's going on?
Seemingly distant, but still close…
This sticky feeling.
Take that off now.
Do what?
We have to disinfect the wound.
Mr. Hong said to make sure to do it.
Right.
I can do this myself.
Is your arm two meters long or something?
How will you disinfect
a wound on your back?
Really, it's okay.
Hurry up.
You said you were a good fighter.
That was a total lie.
You got hurt badly.
I guess you were so shocked
that you didn't see it properly.
I took on almost 20 guys from the start.
Zip it.
Anyway, thank you for saving me.
Even if we're breaking up,
I'm still grateful.
While I was living with you…
I felt so secure.
No matter how dangerous things got,
I wasn't afraid.
Even the world's tallest mountain
wouldn't have stood taller than your back.
Thank you so much
for risking your life to save me.
Just wait a little bit.
I'll protect you now.
I promise I will.
-Touch.
-Keep your guard up.
37 YEARS AGO
Move back.
Keep your guard up.
Hello, sir!
Nice to meet you. I'm Hong Do-yeop.
I'm Baek Sang-gil. I just joined.
I've been a fan since the Asian Games.
You're my role model.
I see.
You lost.
Has it been about 30 years or so?
I think you had about a dozen bottles here
back then too.
You have a good memory.
Back then, I…
really felt like shit.
I thought drinking hard liquor
would help me feel better.
What is it?
Angry about something today too?
Like back then?
Angry?
It's not anger. What should I call it?
It feels filthier than that.
A filthy sense of defeat.
It's been a long time
since I felt this filthy feeling.
Back then, I didn't know what to do
about this feeling.
I think I know now.
One thing can cover up a sense of defeat.
Winning.
This time…
I must win no matter what.
RETURNED
Look.
I have a lot of underwear in here.
Can you leave?
Right, sure.
I found it.
When you get there,
please let me know her destination.
Goodness, if you're so worried,
why don't you take her there yourself?
I want to, but she insists
she doesn't want me to.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
I'll get going now.
Take care of yourself.
Go Eun-sae.
Even though you said we're breaking up…
I still like you.
So if you're ever in danger
or scared,
or if anything happens…
If you need help,
feel free to call me anytime.
It's okay to do that.
I will call when I get there.
But not you. I'll call Jeong-hwa.
Jang Tae-ha, you seriously…
She never took out that suit
or the sneakers while she was here.
But she decided to take them?
Call and ask them to send it back
right away.
Something important is in there.
HONG DO-YEOP
Yes?
Are you with Gang-rok by any chance?
I'm not. Why?
I wanted to eat with him, but I haven't
been able to reach him for a while.
I'll go to his place.
Okay, do that.
Gang-rok!
Kim Gang-rok.
Where did he go?
Baek Sang-gil knows that you're here
and that you helped me.
You should be careful.
KIM GANG-ROK
MY CURRENT LOCATION
Hey, watch out!
Is this bastard crazy?
Hey, you bastard!
You son of a bitch!
Gang-rok, stay with me.
Gang-rok!
I told you I'm a good fighter.
Why did you come here?
Hold on to me.
Hang in there.
Just until we get to the hospital.
Jeong-hwa!
Damn it! Jeong-hwa!
My Jeong-hwa.
OUR STICKY LOVE
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi